http://www.jekkasherbfarm.com/pages/jekkas-privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?When a customer account is created, the personal information collected by our website includes: name, address, email and password. This can be easily accessed via ‘my account page.’ Our website does not store any payment details.
Orders are downloaded by Shopify and information such as delivery and invoice addresses are only used to process and dispatch orders.
Purchase history is stored for our annual customers to ensure we can provide future assistance with growing advice.  If a customer has not placed an order within 3 years then all their data is deleted from our database and website.
Our website is linked to Google Analytics.  This software has tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information, and methods used to browse away from the page. This information just provides us with information about our audience.
How do we collect information?When you place an order and conduct a transaction on our website, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address as part of the process.  Your personal information will be only be used in conjunction with your order.
How do we store information?Our website and database are hosted on a secure server behind a firewall.  Appropriate technical and organisational security measures are in place with a documented security programme that specifies the technical, administrative and physical safeguards for personal data. Our organisation has a documented privacy and security incident response plan.
Online Payments:Payments are processed by Shopify, we do not have access to customers payment or banking details, nor do we store this information. Shopify and our company adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.
Payments over the phone:If payments are taken over the phone, information is processed directly into the cardnet terminal and a copy of the receipt is attached to the invoice which is then sent to the customer.
How do we communicate with youCustomers sign up to our newsletter via a form on our website. Their name and email address are stored in mailchimp and they have easy access to this data.  An unsubscribe button is attached to all of our newsletters.
Customers and account holders are not added to our newsletter subscription, they are required to sign up to this independently.
We do not share any customer data with a third party nor do we obtain data from a third party.
Sign up to our Newsletter
"Close (esc)"
"Close (esc)"
